Finding aid for the J. Paul Getty Trust Press Releases and Public Outreach Materials, 1954-1959, 1973-2022 (bulk 1983-2022) IA10011
Institutional Records and Archives
- Press kits, 1954; 1973,; 1983-1984,; 1989-2020; Series III.; 12.69 Linear Feet (24 boxes)
  - 2002:
    - Railroad Visions, March 5-June 23, 2002 (Box 2021.IA.29-26)
    - The Sacred Spaces of Pieter Saenredam, April 16-July 7, 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)
    - Gustave Le Grey, July 9-September 29, 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)
    - About Life, the Photographs of Dorothea Lange; The Grapes of Wrath, Horace Bristol's California Photographs, October 15, 2002-February 9, 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)
    - Greuze, the Draftsman, November 10-December 1, 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)
  - 2003:
    - Bill Viola, The Passions, January 24-April 27, 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)
    - Surrealist Muse: Lee Miller, Roland Penrose, and Man Ray, February 25-June 15, 2003 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
    - Illuminating the Renaissance, The Triumph of Flemish Manuscript Painting in Europe, June 17-September 7, 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)
    - Strange Days, Photographs from the Sixties by Winograd, Eggleston, and Arbus; Photographs of Artists by Alexander Liberman, July 1-October 19, 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)
    - Julia Margaret Cameron, Photographer, October 21, 2003-January 11, 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-04)
    - Jean-Antoine Houdon, Sculptor of the Enlightenment, November 4, 2003-January 25, 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)
    - Media pack, 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-04)
    - Photographs of Artists by Alexander Liberman, July 22, 2003-October 19, 2003 (Box 2019.IA.03-12)
  - 2004:
    - Illuminated Manuscripts Collection at the Getty Center, 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-04)
    - Media pack, 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-04)
    - Second annual press luncheon, January 19, 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - 38 Photographers of Genius at the Getty, March 16-July 25, 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-04)
    - The Business of Art, Press Viewing Event, March 30, 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-12)
    - Building Music, May 21-June 13, 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - Spirit into Matter, the Photographs of Edmund Teske, June 15-September 26, 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-04)
    - Family Fun at the Getty, August 10, 2004 (Box 2021.IA.29-26)
      Issued for opening of the redesigned Family Room at the Getty Center.
    - Coming of Age in Ancient Greece, September 14-December 5, 2004 (Box 2019.IA.03-04)
    - Einstein at the Skirball, September 14, 2004-May 29, 2005 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
      Skirball Center exhibition presented in collaboration with the J. Paul Getty Trust.
    - Close to Home an American Family Album, October 12, 2004-January 16, 2005 (Box 2021.IA.29-26)
  - 2005:
    - A French Revolution, 3 Exhibitions at the Getty Center: Jacques-Louis David, Empire to Exile; Drawn to Rome, French Neoclassical Sketchbooks and Prints; A Revolutionary Age, Drawing in Europe, January 18-May 1, 2005 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - All the Mighty World, the Photographs of Roger Fenton, February 1-April 24, 2005 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - American Visions: Three Roads Taken, the Photographs of Paul Strand; The Photographs of Frederick Sommer: A Centennial Tribute; Scene of the Crime, Photo by Weegee; Pictures for the Press, May 10, 2005-January 22, 2006 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - The Artist Turns to the Book, May 24-September 11, 2005 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - Rembrandt Late Religious Portraits, June 7-August 28, 2005 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - Painted Prayers, Books of Hours from the Morgan Library, October 18, 2005-January 8, 2006 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - J.Paul Getty Trust Third Annual Press Luncheon, January 24, 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - New and Noteworthy at the Getty - Press Review Event, January 24, 2005 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
  - 2006:
    - The Getty Villa opening, January 28, 2006 (Box 2019.IA.03-04)
    - Antiquity and Photography, Early Views of Ancient Mediterranean Sites, January 28-May 1, 2006 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - Robert Adams, Landscapes of Harmony and Dissonance, February 7-May 28, 2006 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - Agitated Images, John Heartfield and German Photomontage 1920-1938, February 21-June 25, 2006 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - Courbet and the Modern Landscape, February 21-May 14, 2006 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - Degas at the Getty, March 7-June 11, 2006 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
      Contains exhibition brochure and exhibition-branded stationary.
    - Los Angeles Philharmonic Presents Minimalist Jukebox [collaboration with GRI], January 9-April 2, 2006 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - James Ensor's Graphic Modernism, May 2-July 30, 2006 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - The Colors of Clay, Special Techniques in Athenian Vases, June 8-September 4, 2006 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - Eliot Porter in the Realm of Nature, June 13-September 17, 2006 (Box 2014.IA.16-01)
    - Rubens and Brueghel, a Working Friendship, July 5-September 24, 2006 (Box 2014.IA.16-02)
    - A Tumultuous Assembly, Visual Poems of the Italian Futurists, August 1, 2006-January 7, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-02)
    - Hippolytos, Endearing Myth: The Tragedy of Hippolytos and Phaidra, August 24-December 4, 2006; [Getty Villa theater program's inagural production and accompanying exhibition] (Box 2014.IA.16-02)
    - L.A. Press Luncheon kit, September 12, 2006 (Box 2019.IA.03-12)
      Materials housed in a grey branded carry case.
    - From Caspar David Friedrich to Gerhard Richter, German Paintings from Dresden, October 5, 2006-April 29, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-02)
    - Public Faces, Private Faces, Recent Acquisitions, October 10, 2006-February 4, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-02)
    - Guercino, Mind to Paper, October 17, 2006-January 21, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-02)
    - Where We Live: American Photographs from the Berman Collection, October 24, 2006-February 25, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-02)
    - Stories in Stone, Conserving Mosaics of Roman Africa, Masterpieces from the National Museums of Tunisia, October 26, 2006-April 30, 2007 (Box 2019.IA.03-04)
    - Holy Image, Hallowed Ground: Icons from Sinai, November 14, 2006-March 4, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-02)
      Includes CD containing electronic versions of the hardcopy materials.
    - Community Photoworks, Seventh Grade Students Share Their Words and Vision, March 8-12, 2006 (Box 2019.IA.03-04)
    - Julius Shulman, Modernity and the Metropolis, October 11, 2006-January 22, 2007 (Box 2019.IA.03-12)
  - 2007:
    - Zoopsia, New Works by Tim Hawkinson, March 6-September 9, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-02)
    - Oudry's Painted Menagerie, May 1-September 2, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-02)
    - The Old Order and the New, Peter Henry Emerson, John Humble, A Place in the Sun, March 27-July 8, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-02)
    - Greeks on the Black Sea, Ancient Art from the Hermitage, June 14-September 3, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-02)
    - Evidence of Movement, July 10-October 7, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-02)
    - The Herculaneum Women, July 12, 2007-October 13, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-03)
    - Recent History, Photographs by Luc Delahaye; Edward Weston, Enduring Vision, July 31-November 25, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-03)
    - Julius Schulman's Los Angeles, October 6, 2007-January 20, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-03)
    - Reflecting Antiquity, Modern Glass Inspired by Ancient Rome, October 18, 2007-January 8, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-03)
    - Medieval Treasures from the Cleveland Museum of Art, October 30, 2007-January 20, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-03)
    - L.A. Press Luncheon kit, September 9, 2007 (Box 2018.IA.15-06)
    - Please Be Seated, September 18, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-03)
    - Danza de la Cabrita, Photographs by Graciela Iturbide; Andre Kertesz, Seven Decades, December 18, 2007-April 18, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-03)
    - The Getty Center, Reflecting on Ten Years, December 13, 2007 (Box 2014.IA.16-03)
      Getty Center 10th anniversary press kit.
    - Edward Weston, Enduring Vision, July 31, 2007-November 25, 2007 (Box 2019.IA.03-12)
    - Recent History, Photographs by Luc Delahaye, July 31, 2007-November 25, 2007 (Box 2019.IA.03-12)
    - Scala Santa Cappella di San Silvestro, June 12, 2007
      Italian language press kit published by Associazione Amici del Santuario della Scala Santa to publicize a series of Getty Foundation grants supporting the conservation of the Scala Santa in Rome.
  - 2008:
    - Consuming Passion, Fragonard's Allegories of Love, February 12-May 4, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-03)
    - The Color of Life, March 6-June 23, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-03)
    - California Video, March 15-June 8, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-03)
    - August Sander, People of the Twentieth Century; Bernd and Hilla Becher, Basic Forms, May 6-September 14, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-03)
    - Maria Sibylla Merian and Daughters, Women of Art and Science, February 23-May 18, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
    - Bernini and the Birth of Baroque Portrait Sculpture, August 5-October 26, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
    - The Society of Dilettanti, August 7-October 27, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
    - The Marvel and Measure of Peru, July 8-October 19, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
      Includes exhibition brochure in English and Spanish.
    - Agamemnon by Aeschylus, September 4-27, 2008 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
      Annual outdoor theater production at the Getty Villa.
    - Carlton Watkins, Dialogue Among Giants, October 14, 2008-March 1, 2009 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
    - Jim Dine, Poet Singing, October 30, 2008-February 9, 2009 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
    - Tango with Cows, Book Art of the Russian Avant-Garde, November 18, 2008-April 19, 2009 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
      Contains exhibition flyer only.
    - The Belles Heures of the Duke of Berry, November 18, 2008-February 8, 2009 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
    - Captured Emotions, Baroque Painting in Bologna, December 16, 2008-May 3, 2009 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
    - III: Reconstructing Identity, a Statue of a God from Dresden; Fragment to Vase, Approaches to Ceramic Restoration; The Getty Commodus, Roman Portraits and Modern Copies, December 18, 2008-June 1, 2009 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
    - L.A. Press Luncheon kit, September 9, 2008 (Box 2018.IA.15-07)
  - 2009:
    - Paul Outerbridge, Jo Ann Callis, Taking Shape, Made for Manufacture, March 31-July 5, 2009 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
    - Walls of Algiers, Narratives of the City, May 19-October 18, 2009 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
    - Cast in Bronze, French Sculpture from Renaisance to Revolution, June 30-September 27, 2009 (Box 2014.IA.16-04)
    - The Chimaera of Arezzo, The Golden Graves of Ancient Vanni, July 16-October 5, 2009 (Box 2014.IA.16-05)
    - Irving Penn, Small Trades, September 9, 2009-January 10, 2010 (Box 2014.IA.16-05)
    - Aristophanes' Peace, September 10-October 3, 2009 (Box 2014.IA.16-05)
    - Drawings by Rembrandt and His Pupils, December 8, 2009-February 28, 2010 (Box 2014.IA.16-05)
    - The Golden Graves of Ancient Vani, July 16-October 5, 2009 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
  - 2010:
    - A Record of Emotion, The Photographs of Frederick H. Evans, February 2-June 6, 2010 (Box 2014.IA.16-05)
    - Leonardo da Vinci and the Art of Sculpture, March 23-June 20, 2010 (Box 2014.IA.16-05)
    - The Aztec Pantheon and the Art of Empire, March 24-July 5, 2010 (Box 2014.IA.16-05)
    - The Spectacular Art of Jean-Leon Gerome, October 18, 2010-January 23, 2011 (Box 2014.IA.16-05)
    - Engaged Observers, Documentary Photography Since the Sixties, June 29-November 14, 2010 (Box 2014.IA.16-05)
    - The Art of Ancient Greek Theater, August 26, 2010-January 3, 2011 (Box 2014.IA.16-05)
      Contains press release and information for Sophocles' Elektra, the 2010 annual outdoor theater production at the Getty Villa.
    - Imagining the Past in France, November 16, 2010-February 6, 2011 (Box 2014.IA.16-05)
    - Felice Beato, A Photographer on the Eastern Road, December 7, 2010-April 24, 2011 (Box 2014.IA.16-05)
    - The Spectacular Art of Gerome, June 15-September 12, 2010 (Box 2019.IA.03-04)
    - The Chimaera of Arezzo, July 16, 2009-February 8, 2010 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - Urban Panoramas: Opie, Liao, Kim, February 2-June 6, 2010 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - Pacific Standard Time Art in L.A, 1945 - 1980, 2010 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - The Getty, 2010 (Box 2020.IA.04-02)
  - 2011:
    - Pacific Standard Time: Art in L.A. marketing brochure, 2011
    - Gods of Angkor, Bronzes from the National Museum of Cambodia, February 22-August 14, 2011 (Box 2014.IA.16-06)
    - Apollo from Pompeii, Investigating an Ancient Bronze, March 2-September 12, 2011 (Box 2014.IA.16-06)
    - Pacific Standard Time Art in L.A. French language press kit, April 4, 2011
    - Paris Life and Luxury, April 26-August 7, 2011 (Box 2014.IA.16-06)
    - A Revolutionary Project, Cuba from Walker Evans to Now, May 17-October 2, 2011 (Box 2014.IA.16-06)
    - A Nation Emerges, The Mexican Revolution Revealed, September 8, 2011-June 3, 2012 (Box 2014.IA.16-06)
    - Pacific Standard Time at the Getty Center, September 13, 2011-May 6, 2012 (Box 2014.IA.16-06)
    - Modern Antiquity, Picasso, de Chirico, Leger, and Picabia in the Presence of the Antique, November 2, 2011-January 16, 2012 (Box 2014.IA.16-06)
    - Aphrodite and the Gods of Love, March 28-July 9, 2012 (Box 2014.IA.16-06)
    - In Search of Biblical Lands, From Jerusalem to Jordan in 19th-Century Photography, March 2-September 12, 2011 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
  - 2012:
    - Lyonel Feininger Photographs; Narrative Interventions in Photography, October 25, 2011-March 11, 2012 (Box 2014.IA.16-06)
    - Herb Ritts L.A. Style; Portraits of Renown, Photography and the Cult of Celebrity, April 3-August 26, 2012 (Box 2014.IA.16-06)
    - Gustav Klimt, The Magic of the Line, July 3-September 23, 2012 (Box 2014.IA.16-06)
    - Lion Attacking a Horse from the Capitoline Museums, Rome, August 10, 2012-February 4, 2013 (Box 2014.IA.16-06)
      Contains exhibition opening invitation and exhibition flyer only.
    - The Last Days of Pompeii, September 12, 2012-January 7, 2013 (Box 2014.IA.16-06)
    - The Photographs of Ray K. Metzker and the Institute of Design, September 25, 2012-February 24, 2013 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - Florence at the Dawn of the Renaissance, November 13, 2012-February 10, 2013 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - Aphrodite and the Gods of Love, March 28-July 9, 2012 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
  - 2013:
    - Canterbury and St. Albans, Treasures from Church and Cloister, September 20, 2013-February 2, 2014 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - Connecting Seas, A Visual History of Discoveries and Encounters, December 7, 2013-April 13, 2014 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
  - 2014:
    - A Royal Passion, Queen Victoria and Photography; Hiroshi Sugimoto, Past Tense, February 4-June 8, 2014 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - Jackson Pollock's Mural, March 11-June 1, 2014 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - Heaven and Earth, Art of Byzantium from Greek Collections, Byzantium Illumination at the Cultural Crossroads, March 25-August 25, 2014 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - No Further West, The Story of Los Angeles Union Station, May 2-August 10, 2014 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - Pacific Standard Time: LA/LA, May 6, 2014 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - Yvonne Rainer, Dances and Films, May 27-October 12, 2014 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - The Scandalous Art of James Ensor, June 10-September 7, 2014 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - Minor White, Manifestations of the Spirit, July 8-October 19, 2014 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - Persians by Aeschylus, September 4-27, 2014 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - Spectacular Rubens, The Triumph of the Eucharist, October 14, 2014-January 11, 2015 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - Josef Koudelka, Nationality Doubtful, November 11, 2014-March 22, 2015 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - World War I, War of Images, Images of War, November 18, 2014-April 19, 2015 (Box 2014.IA.16-07)
    - Pacific Standard Time: LA/LA [for donors and sponsors], May-June 2014 (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
  - 2015:
    - J.M.W. Turner, Painting Set Free, February 24-May 24, 2015 (Box 2015.IA.03-01)
    - Historic Places L.A., February 24, 2015 (Box 2015.IA.03-01)
    - Light, Paper, Process, Reinventing Photography, April 14-September 6, 2015 (Box 2015.IA.03-01)
    - A Kingdom of Images, French Prints in the Age of Louis XIV, June 16-September 6, 2015 (Box 2015.IA.03-01)
    - Andrea del Sarto, the Renaissance Workshop in Action, June 23-September 13, 2015 (Box 2015.IA.03-01)
    - Cave Temples of Dunhuang, Buddhist Art on China's Silk Road, July 15, 2015 (Box 2015.IA.03-01)
      Includes press release announcing exhibition opening in May 2016, sponsor fact sheets, and other materials in English and Chinese language.
    - Power and Pathos, Bronze Sculpture of the Hellenistic World, July 28-November 1, 2015 (Box 2015.IA.03-01)
    - A Medea in Los Angeles, September 10-October 3, 2015 (Box 2015.IA.03-01)
      Annual outdoor theater production at the Getty Villa. Includes press releases in English and Spanish language.
    - The Younger Generation, Contemporary Japanese Photography, and Ishiuchi Miyako, Postwar Shadows, October 6, 2015-February 21, 2016 (Box 2015.IA.03-01)
      Includes press release in English and Japanese language.
    - The Edible Monument: The Art of Food for Festivals, October 13, 2015-March 13, 2016 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
    - Greece's Enchanting Landscape: Watercolors by Edward Dodwell and Simone Pomardi, October 21, 2015-February 15, 2016 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
    - Woven Gold: Tapestries of Louis XIV, December 15, 2015-May 1, 2016 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
  - 2016:
    - Noir: The Romance of Black in 19th Century French Drawings and Prints, February 9-May 15, 2016 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
    - Robert Mapplethorpe: The Perfect Medium, March 15-July 31, 2016 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
      The Getty exhibition is one part of a two-venue museum retrospective with the Los Angeles County Museum of Art (LACMA).
    - Cave Temples of Dunhuang, Buddhist Art on China's Silk Road, February 10, 2016 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
      Includes press release and sponsor fact sheets, in English and Chinese language. This is the second press kit released for the exhibition.
    - Cave Temples of Dunhuang, Buddhist Art on China's Silk Road, May 7-September 4, 2016 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
      Includes press release and sponsor fact sheets, in English and Chinese language. This is the third press kit released for the exhibition.
    - Roman Mosaics across the Empire, March 30-September 12, 2016 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
    - London Calling, July 26-November 13, 2016 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
    - Richard Learoyd in the Studio, Real/Ideal: Photography in France, August 30-November 27, 2016 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
    - The Art of Alchemy, The Shimmer of Gold, The Alchemy of Color in Medieval Manuscripts, October 11, 2016-February 12, 2017 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
    - Breaking News: Turning the Lens on Mass Media, December 20, 2016-April 30, 2017 (Box 2016.IA.03-01)
  - 2017:
    - Bouchardon, Royal Artist of the Enlightenment, January 10-April 2, 2017 (Box 2017.IA.03-01)
    - The Legacy of Ancient Palmyra, February 18, 2017 (Box 2017.IA.03-01)
      GRI online exhibition. The exhibition was accesible on Getty.edu as of May 11, 2020.
    - Concrete Poetry, Words and Sounds in Graphic Space, March 28-July 30, 2017 (Box 2017.IA.03-01)
    - Eyewitness Views, Making History in Eighteenth-Century Europe, May 9-July 30, 2017 (Box 2017.IA.03-01)
    - Pacific Standard Time LA/LA press preview kit, September 2017-January 2018 (Box 2017.IA.03-01)
      Includes thumb drive containing electronic versions of the hardcopy materials.
    - Thomas Annan Photographer of Glasgow; Now, Then, Chris Killip and the Making of In Flagrante, May 23-August 13, 2017 (Box 2017.IA.03-01)
    - Pacific Standard Time LA/LA Spanish language press kit, September 2017-January 2018 (Box 2017.IA.03-01)
    - Pacific Standard Time LA/LA Portuguese language press kit, September 2017-January 2018 (Box 2017.IA.03-01)
    - Pacific Standard Time LA/LA opening celebration invitation, September 15, 2017 (Box 2017.IA.03-01)
    - Iphigenia in Aulis, September 7-30, 2017 (Box 2017.IA.03-01)
      Annual Getty Villa Theatre production.
    - Sacred Landscapes, Nature in Renaissance Manuscripts; Giovanni Bellini, Landscapes of Faith in Renaissance Venice, October 10, 2017-January 14, 2018 (Box 2017.IA.03-01)
    - Pacific Standard Time LA/LA, September 2017-January 2018 (Box 2017.IA.03-02)
      Contains 2 versions of the press kit, press clips book, photos of the exhibition launch party, and three promotional buttons, stored in a PST: LA/LA branded tote bag.
    - Getty Center celebrates 20th anniversary, Robert Polidori photographs exhibition, December 11, 2017 (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
    - Pacific Standard Time: LA/LA Latin America and Latino Art in LA, for teachers, April 2017 (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
    - Pacific Standard Time: LA/LA Latin American and Latino Art in L.A., September 12, 2017
  - 2018:
    - Harald Szeemann, Museum of Obsessions, February 6-May 6, 2018 (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
    - Cut! Paper Play in Contemporary Photography, February 27-May 27, 2018 (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
    - Paper Promises, Early American Photography, February 27-May 27, 2018 (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
    - Rembrandt and the Inspiration of India, March 13-June 24, 2018 (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
    - Beyond the Nile, Egypt and the Classical World, March 27-September 9, 2018 (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
    - The Getty Villa Reinstallation, April 18, 2018 (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
      Includes press release for the exhibition Plato in L.A.: Contemporary Artitists' Visions, April 19-September 3, 2018.
    - Promote, Tolerate, Ban, Art and Culture in Cold War Hungary, at the Wende Museum of the Cold War, May 20-August 26, 2018 (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
    - In Focus, Expressions, May 22-October 7, 2018 (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
    - Icons of Style, A Century of Fashion Photography, 1911-2011, June 26-October 21, 2018 (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
    - Artists and Their Books, Books and Their Artists, June 26-October 28, 2018 (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
    - Masterful Likeness, Dutch Drawings of the Golden Age, July 24-October 28, 2018 (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
    - Art of Three Faiths, A Torah, A Bible, and a Qur'an, August 7, 2018-February 3, 2019 (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
    - All that Glitters, Life at the Renaissance Court, August 28-December 2, 2018 (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
    - The Renaissance Nude, October 30, 2018-January 27, 2019 (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
    - Underworld, Imagining the Afterlife, October 31, 2018-March 18, 2019 (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
    - MONUMENTality, December 4, 2018-April 21, 2019 (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
  - 2019:
    - Press kit covers, 2019 (Box 2021.IA.29-26)
      Includes press kit covers for: Book of Beasts, the Bestiary in the Medieval World, May 14-August 18, 2019; Bauhaus Beginnings, June 11-October 13, 2019; Buried by Vesuvius, June 26-October 28, 2019; Gordon Parks the Flavio Story, July 9-November 10, 2019.
  - 2020:
    - Michelangelo: Mind of the Master, February 25-June 7, 2020 (Box 2021.IA.29-26)
- Calendars, 1975-2022; Series IV.; 4.99 Linear Feet (9 boxes); 0.1316 GB (184 files)
  Access to digital files in 2017.IA.03, 2018.IA.03, 2019.IA.03, 2020.IA.04, 2021.IA.04 and 2022.IA.04 is available online through the links provided in the inventory.
  These calendars in hardcopy and digital format document the public events that took place at the J. Paul Getty Museum (Malibu) and the Getty Center and date from 1975 to 2022. The calendars intend to periodically inform the general public about exhibitions, performances, tours, courses, and other happenings, and provide dates, times and other details about how to attend. The name of the calendar has been periodically changed over time, and these titles are reflected in the inventory headings. Calendars published in press release format, and intended for media editors, are located in Series I. Chronological press releases.